callwave.com 2006-12-16

# Privacy Policy

About CallWave  
Investor Relations  
Press Room

 **Award Winner!**  

  | 

Privacy Policy

CallWave, Inc. ("CallWave") has created this Privacy Statement (the "Statement") as part of its commitment to protecting its Members (the "Members") personal information from misuse when using CallWave Service(s), as defined in CallWave's Terms of Service for CallWave, Inc. (the "Terms of Service").

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the CallWave website, found at www.callwave.com, CallWave's business practices and its employees.

This Privacy Statement contains specific information about the following:

  1. Message Content Handling
  2. CallWave Information Collection and Use
  3. Communication
  4. Partner Advertising
  5. CallWave Information Sharing
  6. Co-branded Partners
  7. Safeguarding Privacy
  8. Notification of Changes
  9. Contact Information

* * *

  1. **Message Content Handling**

CallWave software-based service(s) are delivered through its proprietary Enhanced Services Platform, which allows Members to manage calls across their existing landline, mobile and Internet networks.

CallWave representatives will not view or listen to the contents of Member's private communications as part of its routine procedure. However, in order to determine the cause of technical problems or to determine where a communications needs to be sent CallWave representatives may need to view or listen to said communications. The only other instance in which the content of Member's communication would be seen or heard by CallWave is if CallWave is required to disclose the contents by applicable law, by order of a court (or other governmental body or arbitrator) of competent jurisdiction or to protect the safety of any person or the integrity of any property rights.

As a result, CallWave cannot guarantee that the content of Member's transmissions will never be seen and that the content of Member's voice messages will never be heard by CallWave personnel.

  2. **CallWave Information Collection and Use**
    1. **General Tracking Information:**  
CallWave tracks Member's traffic patterns throughout the CallWave website and also collects information about the telephone numbers used to place calls into CallWave's Enhanced Services Platform. However, CallWave does not correlate this information with data about individual Members. CallWave does break down overall usage statistics according to a Member's domain name, browser type, IP address, operating system and MIME type. CallWave uses Member's IP address to help diagnose the CallWave servers and to administer the CallWave website. CallWave uses various technical information about Member's computer operating environment to help it properly configure, diagnose, and monitor CallWave Service(s) and usage.
    2. **Registration:**  
In order to register for the CallWave Service(s), Member must give their name, email address, mailing address, home phone number, cell phone number and other information that may be reasonably requested from time-to-time. CallWave also may ask several questions about Member's Internet usage, telephone service usage, and general demographic information (income, etc.). The information CallWave receives at registration helps it better understand how to tailor the CallWave site and its Service(s) to meet Members' needs. The collected information also helps CallWave to understand the demographics of Members. Because CallWave may derive revenue from advertising, obtaining demographic data is essential. CallWave will exercise its best efforts not to disclose a Member's personally identifiable information to third parties unless it (1) receives permission from the Member; (2) is required to disclose such information by any applicable law or legal process served on CallWave; (3) needs to disclose the information to enforce the CallWave Terms of Service.
    3. **Cookies:**  
CallWave may use cookies to deliver content specific to Member's interests, to save Member's password so that they do not need to reenter it during each visit to the CallWave website, and for other purposes. CallWave may deliver a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates. Members can easily configure their browser to turn off cookies.
    4. **Credit Card Information:**  
CallWave may ask for credit card information so that it can fulfill Member's order, and so that it can provide this information only to the company or companies who process Member's credit card payment. CallWave will not share Member's credit card information with any third party other than those necessary to process payments.
    5. **Action Tags:**  
CallWave may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on its behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If Members would like more information about this practice and their choices, please go to http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp.

  3. **Communication**

CallWave administers email and "pop-up" communications for the benefit of its Members. These communications may include the following: announcements about new products and/or advertisements from CallWave and its partners; answers to customer inquiries; changes in service and feature availability; changes to CallWave's Terms of Service; invitations to participate in questionnaires about the CallWave Service(s); and an optional newsletter containing special offers and/or tips on how to better use the service. There are instructions at the bottom of each email message on how to unsubscribe. Some notices are mandatory, such as service announcements. CallWave may utilize the services of a third-party to facilitate such mailings.

If, at any time, Member wishes to stop receiving email messages from CallWave, Member must (1) terminate Member's CallWave account, as described in the CallWave Terms of Service, and (2) submit Member's name to CallWave's Email Opt Out page at http://www.callwave.com/emailOptOut.asp.

  4. **Partner Advertising**

When a Member clicks on an advertisement sent by CallWave, CallWave will be notified that the Member clicked on that particular ad. This "click-through" information will be used to tailor certain promotional offers to the Member in the future (based on which offers the Member clicked on in the past).

  5. **CallWave Information Sharing**

CallWave uses the information it gathers to tailor its content to suit Members' needs and to help its advertisers better understand the Members' demographics. CallWave will provide that information in aggregate form to its advertisers. CallWave's intention is to never share Member's personally identifiable information with third parties. CallWave will only release a Member's personally identifiable information to a third party if (1) CallWave receives permission from the Member, or (2) are required to disclose such information by any applicable law or legal process served on CallWave, or (3) need to disclose the information to enforce the CallWave Terms of Service, or (4) need to do so as part of an arrangement with a Co-branded partner (see Section 6: Co-Branded partners for further explanation).

The CallWave website may contain links to other websites. CallWave is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In the case of a merger or acquisition, personally identifiable information is deemed related to the primary purpose for which the information was collected and therefore may be one of the transferred assets.

  6. **Co-branded Partners**

From time-to-time, CallWave partners with other service/application providers to develop a co-brand partnership. These co-branded service/applications are offered to CallWave Members through various CallWave communication campaigns. If CallWave Members accept the co-branded offer CallWave will share with its co-brand partner Members demographic information to assist co-brand partner in tailoring its advertising content based on Member preferences. CallWave only shares the demographic information belonging to Members who accept the co-brand offer. By accepting the co-brand offer, Member grants CallWave permission to share demographic information with co-brand partner. CallWave will not share Member information belonging to Members who do not accept co-brand offer.

  7. **Safeguarding Privacy**

CallWave takes the issue of safeguarding Member's privacy online seriously. CallWave exercises great care in securing Member's personally identifiable information. Internally, CallWave restricts access to personally identifiable information to employees who need access to the information in order to perform their duties. These employees are very limited in number and are committed to Member's privacy and security policies. CallWave has had its employees execute comprehensive nondisclosure agreements, which provide explicit legal confidentiality protections. CallWave reviews its web security, and its security policy and practices, with employees on a regular basis.

  8. **Notification of Changes**

CallWave may edit this Privacy Statement from time to time. If, at some point in the future, there is a change to CallWave's information usage practices that affects Member's personally identifiable information, CallWave will notify Member by posting a prominent notice on its Privacy Statement or on its home page. If Member disagrees with these changes, they may cancel their CallWave Service(s).

  9. **Contact Information**

If Member has any questions about this Privacy Statement, Member can send an email to privacy@callwave.com. For general questions about CallWave, please go to our Customer Service area on the web by clicking here.

CallWave, Inc.  
P.O. Box 549  
Santa Barbara, CA 93102

|
